solutd.com 2018-08-22

# privacy

(Dit PRIVACY STATEMENT is tevens beschikbaar in het Nederlands)

Our Privacy Statement for Advertisement is located [here](http://ads.solutd.com/adsprivacy.html).

SOL United takes the privacy of its users very seriously, and will ensure that all data and information about you in the possession of SOL United is processed and used securely. This document outlines the Privacy Policy of SOL United. We advise you to read this Privacy Policy very carefully. Words in this Privacy Policy written with an initial capital letter are defined in the SOL United terms of use (which can be found here).

### 1\. Who is SOL United? 

SOL United is a business that offers an online platform for content of social opinion leaders, celebrities or high-profile people who have or will have a group of loyal followers on social media. SOL United has its registered office in Amsterdam (postal code 1087 KA) and its business offices in Amsterdam at Valeriusstraat 117 (postal code 1075 ER). SOL United is registered in the Chamber of Commerce under number 53284135. The processing of Personal Data by SOL United is registered with the Dutch Data Protection Authority under number m1498381.

### 2\. What information does SOL United collect and process?

#### Account 

For optimum use of the Service that SOL United offers, a User must create a personal Account. When you as a User create such an Account, you are asked to provide certain personal information (your name and e-mail address). You may volunteer more information, but you are not required to do so. A user can always edit the information provided in the Account.

#### Automatically Generated Information

SOL United also collects automatically generated information about your surfing habits while using the Service, including but not limited to how often Content is viewed and how many comments given Content has generated. This information includes, but is not limited to, your IP address and the browser (computer program used to view web pages) you are using. SOL United may also use cookies.

### 3\. What are cookies and how does SOL United use them? 

In the performance of the Service, SOL United uses cookies that your browser stores on your computer either temporarily ("session cookies") or for a longer period ("permanent cookies"). Cookies are small files with information that the SOL United server sends to your browser to allow that information to be sent back to the SOL United server upon a subsequent visit to the site.

With a permanent cookie, our Service can recognize you the next time you visit our Web Site, so that the Web Site can be automatically configured to your preferences. This saves you the time of configuring the site for each visit. Session cookies can be used for a number of purposes, such as keeping track of the web pages you visit and the options on the Service that you use. A cookie cannot be used to spread viruses.

You can set your browser to reject cookies the next time you use the Service. If you do, however, some or all of the options of the Service may not function, or you may be blocked from accessing certain components of the Service or the Service as a whole. More information on accepting and blocking cookies can be found in the user guide or the Help section of your browser.

If you do accept cookies, SOL United recommends that you log out whenever you have used the service on a publicly accessible computer and to keep the login information issued to you secret.

### 4\. For what purposes will SOL United use the information collected?

#### Objectives

SOL United will use the collected Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to provide the Service to you in the optimum manner;
  * to facilitate and optimize your use of the Service;
  * to process your complaints, suggestions, Reports and questions;
  * to compile anonymous statistics based on automatically generated information for security purposes relating to the Service;
  * to keep you informed of changes to the Service, including sending you the SOL United newsletter if you have registered for it;
  * to inform you of relevant similar products and/or services of SOL United;
  * to provide your information to third parties, in compliance with legislation and regulations, or where SOL United sees reason to do so pursuant to this Privacy Policy;

#### Use by SOL United

In order to ensure that you as User can post comments on Content, SOL United must process your Personal Data.

SOL United will also process your Personal Data, including name, e-mail address and/or telephone number, to handle any complaints, suggestions, Reports or questions you submit. This will allow SOL United to contact you to respond to your complaint, suggestion, Report or question. 

Additionally, SOL United will keep you informed of changes to the Service. Whenever an expansion or update is implemented, SOL United will inform you. SOL United can also inform you of new Content or actions it organizes. Additionally, SOL United can inform you about similar products or services it offers. You can expect to receive an occasional message from SOL United. You can also register for the SOL United newsletter. If you decide you no longer wish to receive the newsletter, you can unsubscribe by sending an e-mail to unsubscribe@solutd.com. A method of unsubscribing is also given in each individual newsletter. 

#### Use by third parties

SOL United will never provide your Personal Data to third parties for direct marketing purposes (such as sending advertising) without your explicit permission. This means that SOL United will always inform you in advance of any intention to do so.

SOL United also points out that third parties (such as other Users) could gain access to your Personal Data that you yourself place on the public section of the Service. This in any event includes your user name, which is displayed on the Service whenever you place a comment. The information you place by means of the Service may also be indexed by external web sites, such as through likes, retweets, respects and +1s on social media present in the Service or by search engines. SOL United has no control over and is not liable for the ways in which such third parties handle your Personal Data. 

#### Google Analytics

SOL United uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service offered by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies (as described in paragraph 3 above) in order to help SOL United analyse how you use the Services. The information generated by the cookie (including your IP address) is transferred to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google uses this information for SOL United to track how you use the Service, to draft reports for SOL United on the web site activity, and to offer other services relating to the web site activity and internet use. Google can provide this information to third parties if Google is required to do so by law or where said third parties process the information for Google. Google itself will not link your IP address to other information Google has access to. You can reject cookies as described in paragraph 3. 

#### DoubleClick DART

SOL United uses Double Click DART, an advertising service offered by Google. Google uses cookies as described in paragraph 3 to display the advertisements on the Service. The information generated by the cookie (including your IP address) is transferred to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. With the DART cookie, Google can display advertisements based on User visits to the Service, web sites of SOL United, and other web sites. Users may opt out of the DART cookie here. The User can also adjust his/her categories of interest or add categories so as to see more relevant advertisements.

#### Google and Safe Harbor

Google Inc. and all its subsidiaries, including Google Analytics and DoubleClick DART, adhere to the Safe Harbor privacy principles and are members of the Safe Harbor programme of the American Department of Commerce.

### 5\. How does SOL United protect personal information? 

SOL United has taken appropriate technical and organizational steps to protect your Personal Data against loss or any form of illegitimate data processing. 

### 6\. Transfer of business

It may happen in the future that one or more units or assets of SOL United are transferred to a third party or that SOL United merges with a third party. If this happens, your Personal Data may also be transferred to that third party. 

### 7\. Forwarding to countries outside the EU

Because SOL United uses Google Analytics and DoubleClick DART as described above at paragraph 4, certain Personal Data you provide will be forwarded to the United States. The fact that Google is a member of the Safe Harbor programme attests to an appropriate level of protection for the processing of your Personal Data. 

SOL United uses Amazon server services. This means that SOL United transfers your Personal Data to the United States. Amazon is a Safe Harbor member. This means that there is an appropriate level of protection for the processing of your Personal Data.

### 8\. Storage of your information

SOL United will not store your Personal Data longer than necessary for the achievement of the objectives for which it is collected and processed. 

### 9\. Viewing and updating your information

In your Account, you can view and change your Personal Data at any time. If you would like to know what other information SOL United has recorded about you in addition to your Account information, please contact privacy@solutd.com. SOL United will respond within four weeks and inform you of whether SOL United processes any Personal Data about you. If the answer is yes, SOL United will include a list of all Personal Data about you that SOL United processes.

At reasonable intervals, you can request SOL United to correct, add, delete, or protect certain Personal Data about you based on the list provided where this information is factually in error, inadequate for or irrelevant to the goal or objectives of processing, or otherwise processed in violation of any provision of law. SOL United will then inform you within four weeks of whether, and if so, to what extent, SOL United will comply with your request. 

### 10\. What is the scope of SOL United's responsibility?

The Service may contain hyperlinks taking you to third party web sites, by which you leave the Service. SOL United has no control over any third party web sites that are linked to. This means that the use of such third party web sites may be governed by different privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers the Personal Data processed through the Service. SOL United accepts no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the web sites or services of third parties, their functioning and/or their content.

### 11\. Can this privacy policy be changed?

This privacy policy can be changed. Any such changes will be announced through the Service.

### 12\. Any questions?

Should you still have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to privacy@solutd.com.
